---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10&difficulty=easy
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
      User-Agent:
      - Ruby
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Date:
      - Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:24:49 GMT
      Server:
      - Apache
      Expires:
      - Thu, 19 Nov 1981 08:52:00 GMT
      Cache-Control:
      - no-store, no-cache, must-revalidate
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Access-Control-Allow-Origin:
      - "*"
      Set-Cookie:
      - PHPSESSID=25884c76dcf4274ed82915a1e3908d28; path=/
      Upgrade:
      - h2
      Connection:
      - Upgrade
      Vary:
      - User-Agent
      Strict-Transport-Security:
      - max-age=31536000
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who
        is the main character of the game Half-Life: Opposing Force?","correct_answer":"Adrian
        Shephard","incorrect_answers":["Gordon Freeman","Alyx Vance","Barney Calhoun"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which of these
        video game engines was made by the company Epic Games?","correct_answer":"Unreal","incorrect_answers":["Unity","Game
        Maker: Studio","Cry Engine"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"If
        soccer is called football in England, what is American football called in
        England?","correct_answer":"American football","incorrect_answers":["Combball","Handball","Touchdown"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the 2002
        video game &quot;Kingdom Hearts&quot;, how many Keyblades are usable?","correct_answer":"18","incorrect_answers":["13","16","15"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the &quot;Half-Life&quot;
        series, &quot;H.E.V&quot; stands for &quot;Hazardous Evasiveness Vest&quot;","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which one of these
        songs did the group &quot;Men At Work&quot; NOT make?","correct_answer":"Safety
        Dance","incorrect_answers":["Down Under","Who Can It Be Now?","It&#039;s a
        Mistake"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Kanye
        West at 2009 VMA&#039;s interrupted which celebrity?","correct_answer":"Taylor
        Swift","incorrect_answers":["MF DOOM","Beyonce","Beck"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Cartoon & Animations","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        is lost in Hawaiian and is also the name of a little girl in a 2002 film which
        features a alien named &quot;Stitch&quot;?","correct_answer":"Lilo","incorrect_answers":["Lolo","Lucy","Lulu"]},{"category":"Vehicles","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        are the cylinder-like parts that pump up and down within the engine?","correct_answer":"Pistons","incorrect_answers":["Leaf
        Springs","Radiators","ABS"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which
        psychopath(s) in Dead Rising 1 gave you the small chainsaw?","correct_answer":"Adam
        the Clown","incorrect_answers":["Cliff Hudson","The convicts","Larry the butcher"]}]}'
  recorded_at: Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:24:49 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 6.1.0
